Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS.213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Sound recordings, 242013
  - Subseries A: Audio Works, 1976-1985; 197226
    - Contortions Max's Jan 28 '79/ DNA Jerks CBGB Jan 17 '79/ T.J. and the Jerks, Jerks Again Max's May 15 '79, 1979; ID: 213.0077; 197854 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0077, Case 213.0077)
    - Contortions Thanksgiving '78 Nov. 23 Max's one set only, November 23, 1978; ID: 213.0078; 197855 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0078, Case 213.0078_pt.1, Case 213.0078_pt.2)
      Side A and B: [Track Unknown], My Infatuation, I Don't Wanna Be Happy, [Track Unknown], Designed to Kill, [Track Unknown], Roving Eye, Love Twice Removed, Dish It Out, Disposable You, Throw Me Away, Jaded But So in Love, Contort Yourself
    - Contortions Jam Aug 17 '78/ Chain of Fools Soundcheck Max's 2 sets Jam, August 17, 1978; ID: 213.0079; 197856 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0079, Case 213.0079_pt.1, Case 213.0079_pt.2)
      Content: [Can't] Take it, Please Please Me
      [Track Unknown], Dish It Out, My Infatuation, Designed to Kill, Love Twice Removed, I Don't Wanna Be Happy, [Track Unknown], Throw Me Away, Contort Yourself, Can't Stand
    - Valore- The Martini Room, 1994; ID: 213.0080; 197857 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0080, Case 213.0080_pt.1)
      To Love and Be Loved, The Martini Room, Love, Mr. Lucky, The Quiet Time, Cryin', I Wish I'd Never, Fly Hindenberg, Two Ships, All The Time Blues, River
      Tape Length: 92 minutes
      CD currently unavailable.
    - Shame on you, Aerosmith/ Apache-Tequila, undated; ID: 213.0081; 197858 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0081, Case 213.0081)
      Tape Length: 70 minutes
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 213.0082; 197859 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0082, Case 213.0082_pt.1, Case 213.0082_pt.2)
    - Alan Vega, 1983; ID: 213.0083; 197860 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0083, Case 213.0083)
      Content: Molson Golden Fall '83
      Border Crossing, Astronauts, Wine Steward, Camping, Bar, Skiing, Musicians (Concert), Airplane
    - Less Than Zero, undated; ID: 213.0084; 197861 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0084)
      Side A: Rocking Pneumonia And the Boogie Woogie Flu/Aerosmith, Lite Fades Away/Roy Orbision, Rock And Roll All Nite/Poison, Goin' Back To Cali/L.L. Cool J., You and Me(Less Than Zero)/Glen Danzig, In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida/Slayer
      Side B: Bring the Noise/Public Enemy, Are You My Woman/Black Flames, She's Lost You/Joan Jett and the Blackhearts, How to Love Again/Oran Juice Jones and Alyson Williams, Hazy Shade of Winter/Bangles
    - Apes of God - Jeroen Wilhelmus, Michiel Hofmans, Meinbert v Soest, Jacky Simons, undated; ID: 213.0085; 197862 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0085)
    - SWEET/ MEATMEN and other classic muscle tunes, undated; ID: 213.0086; 197863 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0086)
      Side A: Sweet- Fox on the Run, Ballroom Blitz, Action, Someone Else Will; Uriah Heep- Easy Livin; Nazareth- Razamanaz; Meatmen- War of the Superbikes; Dictators- Master Race Rock; Amboy Dukes- Journey to the Center of the Mind; Judas Priest- Steeler; Lucifers Friend- Ride the Sky- Butthole Surfers- Sweatloaf
      Side B: Meatmen- Punkerama, Cum On Over To My Crib, Lesbian Death Dirge, Pillar of Sodom, Centurians of Rome, God's Bullies, Cadaver Class, French People Suck, Wine Wenches Wheels, What's this Shit Called Love, Dance to the Music, Rock + Roll Juggernaut - Tesco's solo EP
    - Jean Caffeine, undated; ID: 213.0087; 197864 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0087)
      Side A: Big Wheel, Hushed Tones, Jesus is Coming Soon (to a theatre near you), That was the Liquor Talkin'
    - Feelies Maxwell's Sunday April 13 1980/ Feelies 2nd Set, ID: 213.0088; 197865 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0088, Case 213.0088_pt.1, Case 213.0088_pt.2)
    - Feelies Sept- Dec 1978 Max's Sept 2nd 1978 (late show)/ Hurrah Dec 12th 1978 (one set), ID: 213.0089; 197866 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0089, Case 213.0089_pt.1, Case 213.0089_pt.2)
      Side A: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Loveless Love, Work, Original Love, [Track Unknown], Crazy Rhythms, Well Alright, Third Ucle
      Side B: Boy, Original Love, Work, Loveless Love, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, [Track Unknown]
    - Voidoids -late show- July 2, 1978 CBGB *Feelies July 2nd II/ Feelies Hurrah July 19, 1978, ID: 213.0090; 197867 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0090, Case 213.0090_pt.1, Case 213.0090_pt.2)
      Side A: Third Uncle, I'm Free, Beware, Walkin, Kid, Amuse
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Night, Work, Loveless Love
    - The Feelies/ MUDD Dec 29, 1978 CBGB Happy Spring Cont'd, December 29, 1978; ID: 213.0091; 197868 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0091, Case 213.0091_pt.1, Case 213.0091_pt.2)
      Side A: Boy, Original Love, Work, [Track Unknown], Fa Ce La, [Track Unknown], Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms, Lookin At You, Third Uncle
      Side B: Boy, Original Love, Work, [Track Unknown], Fa Ce La, Loveless Love, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythm, Lookin At You
    - Cramps Pep lounge Feb 25-26 '83 "Smell of Female", 1983; ID: 213.0092; 197895 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0092, Case 213.0092)
      Tape Length: 20 minutes
    - Commander Cody & His Lost Planet Airmen, Live at the Academy, undated; ID: 213.0093; 197896 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0093, Case 213.0093_pt.1, Case 213.0093_pt.2)
      Side A: Wine Do Your Stuff, Truck Drivin' Man, Seeds 'n' Stems, Lookin' at the World thru a Windshield, Sunset on the Sage, Boogie Man, Daddy's Drinkin up Our Christmas, Diggy Liggy Lo, Sea Cruise, That's What I Like about the South, Ernie's Thing, Andy's Thing
      Side B: Milk Cow Blues, Four/Five Times, I'm Comin' Home, Mama Tried, House of Delights, Oh Mama Mama, Cryin' Time, I Saw the Light, Beat Me Daddy, Hot Rod Lincoln
    - Commander Cody & His Lost Planet Airmen Live/ Johnny M, undated; ID: 213.0094; 197903 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0094, Case 213.0094)
      Side A: Root in Cell #9, Too Much Fun, Don't Let Go, Jailhouse Rock, Mean Woman Blues, Lost in the Ozone, Hey Hey Hey
      Side B: Mahavishnu Orch[estra] Live [wooward race], Miles Davis Sivad
    - Mahavishnu Orchestra Dec 28, 1973, Philharmonic Hall, December 28, 1973; ID: 213.0095; 197908 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0095, Case 213.0095)
      Side A: Dream (cont'd), No Name (Goodman), Love Supreme, Awakening Jam
      Side B. Hope (encore), The Noonward Race
    - Mahavishnu Orchestra Central Park, June 24, 1974, ID: 213.0096; 197910 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0096, Case 213.0096_pt.1, Case 213.0096_pt.2)
      Side A: Power of Love
      Side B: (cont'd) - Smile of the Beyond, Hymn to Him
    - Mahavishnu Live at Ithaca College, Oct 26 1974, October 26, 1974; ID: 213.0097; 197913 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0097, Case 213.0097)
    - Mahavishnu Live in Central Park, June 24, 1974, ID: 213.0098; 197921 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0098, Case 213.0098)
    - David Bowie - July 19, 1974, ID: 213.0099; 197922 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0099, Case 213.0099)
      Side A: 1984, Rebel Rebel, Moonage Daydream, Boys-It's a Sweet Thing- Changes- Suffragette City
      Side B: Alladin Sane, All the Young Dudes, Cracked Actor, Rock n Roll with Me, Watch That Man, Knock on Wood, Space Oddity
      Tape Length:90 minutes
    - Roxy Music live in London Oct 17th 1975, Wembley Empire - Poor Copy, October 17, 1975; ID: 213.0100; 197926 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0100, Case 213.0100_pt.1, Case 213.0100_pt.2)
    - Mahavishnu, Oct 26, 1974 Live at Ithaca College, October 26, 1974; ID: 213.0101; 197927 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0101, Case 213.0101)
    - Chick Corea Return to Forever / Gato, undated; ID: 213.0102; 197928 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0102, Case 213.0102_pt.1, Case 213.0102_pt.2)
    - Oregon Live at the Unicorn April 6th 1975, April 6, 1975; ID: 213.0103; 197929 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0103)
    - Santana Oct 14, 1974/ DR Demento, October 14, 1974; ID: 213.0104; 197930 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0104, Case 213.0104_pt.1, Case 213.0104_pt.2)
    - Santana, undated; ID: 213.0105; 197931 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0105, Case 213.0105)
    - Hell, Glenn O'Brien, Folk City April 25 '84/ Hell, Joey Ramone, [Cramps] April 4, '84 WBAI, 1984; ID: 213.0106; 197932 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0106, Case 213.0106_pt.1, Case 213.0106_pt.2)
      Side A: Richard Hell- Folk City 4-25-84, Glen[n] Obrien- Tramps 4-25-84
      Side B: Richard Hell- WBAI Interview, Joey Ramone Interview
    - Lloyd w/Bidwell New Group Aug 7 '80 CBGB Squat Set 25 '80, 1980; ID: 213.0107; 197933 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0107, Case 213.0107)
    - Lloyd's Quartet - Town Hall, March 30 '80. Dead Boys -same-, March 30, 1980; ID: 213.0108; 197934 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0108, Case 213.0108_pt.1, Case 213.0108_pt.2)
      Side A: She Said No, I Can Tell, Alchemy, Misty Eyes, Now That She Has Gone
    - Lloyd & Co - [Peprum Lounge] Jan 22, 1981, January 22, 1981; ID: 213.0109; 197935 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0109, Case 213.0109)
    - Bloods VOIDOIDS Feb 27 '81 Pep Lounge, February 27, 1981; ID: 213.0110; 197936 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0110, Case 213.0110)
      Side A: Kid, Ignore That Door
    - Hell, Void-Oids CBGB Thursday the [___] of September 1979, two sets, ID: 213.0111; 197939 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0111, Case 213.0111)
      Side A: Kid, [Track Unknown], Lowest Common Dominator, I'm Gone, __ Spurts, Crack of Dawn, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Game of Love, You Gotta Lose, Ignore That Door
      Side B: (?) Spurts, Dominator, [Track Unknown], Staring in Her Eyes, New Pleasure, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Another World, [Track Unknown], Walkin on the Water, Kid, Liars Beware
    - Hell/ Student teacher's, Hell/ 57 Club, March 30 -79, March 30, 1979; ID: 213.0112; 197940 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0112, Case 213.0112)
      Side A: Staring in Her Eye, You Gotta Lose, ___ Spurts, New Pleasure
      Side B: [Track Unknown], Walkin on the Water, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], ___ Spurts, Who Says?, [Track Unknown], Another World
    - Void-Oids & Patti - Palladium May 20 1978, ID: 213.0113; 197941 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0113, Case 213.0113)
      Side A: ___Spurts, Liars Beware, Kid With the Replac[e]able Head, Walkin' on the Water, Blank, I Wanna Be Your Dog
    - Void-Oids, April 20 1978 CBGB Thursday late show with Erasers/ Hell Solo, Bottom Line Aug 1984, 1978/1984; ID: 213.0114; 197944 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0114, Case 213.0114_pt.1, Case 213.0114_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: Venus, Walking in Rain, I Don't Love Anyone, #7, Liars Beware, Kid with the Replac[e]able Head, New Pleasure, Betra[ya]l Takes Two, Ventilator Blues, Spurts, Blank, Be Your Dog, All theWay
    - VoidOids Hell, Max's - Jan 27 '77 2 sets, Aug 18 '78 one set, 1977/1978; ID: 213.0115; 197945 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0115, Case 213.0115_pt.1, Case 213.0115_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: Spurts, Liars Beware, New Pleasure, The Plan, You Gotta Lose, Walkin on the Water, I'm Your Man, Time Stands Still, Blank/Liars Beware, Walkin on the Water, I'm Your Man, Betrayal Takes Two, New Pleasure, Another World, Spurts, Blank/ Blank.
    - Hell, Punk Benefit May 4-5 '77, 1977; ID: 213.0116; 198147 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0116, Case 213.0116)
      Sides A and B: Blank, Walkin on the Water, New Pleasure, Betrayal Takes Two, Rock 'n' Roll Club, Spurts/ Spurts, Liars Beware, Another World, New Pleasure
    - VoidOids, sound check 4/17/77 CBGB/ Patti Smith Group, May 4, 1977 CBGB Punk Benefit with Matthew Reich, ID: 213.0117; 198149 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0117, Case 213.0117)
      Side A: Spurts, I'm Your Man, Ventilator Blues, I Wanna Be Your Dog
      Side B: Kimberly, Pissing in the River, Gimme Some Lovin', Chain Gang, (Boyfriendx), Waiting For My Man
      Format: 1/4" Audiocassette
      Tape Length: 46 minutes
    - Heartbreakers Demos/ VoidOids April 14 '77, 1977; ID: 213.0118; 198150 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0118, Case 213.0118_pt.1, Case 213.0118_pt.2)
      Sides A and B (New Pleasure): Spurts, New Pleasure, Liars Beware, The Plan, You Gotta Lose, Another World, 7. Rock n Roll Club, Blank
    - VoidOids, Max's 27 1-27-77, January 27, 1977; ID: 213.0119; 198151 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0119, Case 213.0119_pt.1, Case 213.0119_pt.2)
      Sides And B: Set I: Spurts, Liars, New Pleasure, Lose, Walking, I'm Your Man, Blank/ Set II: Liars, Walkin', I'm Your Man, Betrayal
      Container Annotation: Richard Hell Voidoids at Max's 11:40-12:10 am; 1:35-2:10 am 65 minutes
      Recording Length (tape annotation): 65 minutes
    - The Void-Oids Live Nov 19th & 20th / Single Patti Smith at Bottom Line Monday 22nd November w/ Lee Fox Bass, undated; ID: 213.0120; 198152 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0120, Case 213.0120_pt.1, Case 213.0120_pt.2)
      Side A: [Track Unknown], Love Comes in Spurts, the Plan, All the Way, Time Stands Still, I'm Your Mom, Blank Generation, [Track Unknown], You Gotta Lose, New Pleasure, The Plan, All the Way, Blank Generation, Love Comes, Another World, You Gotta Lose, Blank Generation
      Side B: Jesse James, Kimberly, Jam/J.A., Ask ME, Angels, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Pumpin'
      R. Hell - Vocal, Bass; Marc Bell - Drums; Ivan Julian - Guitar, Robert Quine - Guitar/Bottom Line Monday 22nd November w/ Lee fox - Bass
    - Shirts - The Heartbreakers Live July 25, 1975 CBGB during RnR Festival summer of '75/Dolls 73/74 Detriot Michigan Place, 1973-1975; ID: 213.0121; 198153 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0121, Case 213.0121)
      Sides A and B: Going Steady, Chinese Rocks, [Pirate Cove], Eyes on You, Flight, Nothin Better To Do, Blank, I Wanna Be Loved, New Pleasure, Flo & Eddie on Lou, Human Being, Pills, Trash, Give Her a Great Big Kiss ([Fla] '74), Chatterbox
      The Hearbreakers 7/25 Live at CBGB during R n' R Festival Summer of '75; Dolls 73/74 Detroit Michigan Palace
    - CBGB Aug 13, 1978- Lloyd, Daugherty, Smith, Fliegler, Brody- zak-Lenny, Lisa Burns, Daugherty-r-guitar & Jesse- Drums, Genja Ravan, H. Goldman, ID: 213.0122; 198154 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0122, Case 213.0122)
      Side A: Pretty Vacant, Love Me Do, Heartaches, Monster Mash (with Zak), Whiter Shade of Pale (with Lenny), Crazy Like a Fox, Tumblin' Dice
      Side B: Lola, Fever, Messin w/the kid
      Lisa Burns, Dougherty - r. guitar, Jesse - drums, [Genja Ravam], H. Goldman
    - Lloyd- Max's Friday Jan 12, 1979, ID: 213.0123; 198155 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0123, Case 213.0123_pt.1, Case 213.0123_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: Watch Yourself, Won't Give Her Up, She Said No, Woman's Ways, Pretend, [Track Unknown], In the Night, Should Have Known Better
    - Lloyd Quartet CBGB March 4th '79, 1979; ID: 213.0124; 198156 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0124, Case 213.0124_pt.1, Case 213.0124_pt.2)
      Side A: Alchemy, Number Nine, Better Watch Yourself, Dying Words, Woman's Ways
    - Lloyd & Co. June 3, 78- Max's Patti [F.] Smith, B. Brady, J.D. Daugherty, R Fleigler, L. Kaye/ Crayola Max's June 4, '78, 1978; ID: 213.0125; 198157 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0125, Case 213.0125_pt.1, Case 213.0125_pt.2)
      Side A (Lloyd): Gimmie Some Lovin', Rebel Rebel, Glad All Over, Back Door Man, Today I Met the Boy..., Under My Thumb, Don't Bring Me Down, Can Ya Hear Me Knockin'
      Side B (Lloyd/Crayola): Miss You
    - Birdland CBGB Jan 3, 1979 2nd Show CBGB/ Lloyd (solo) MUD Jan 5, 1979, ID: 213.0126; 198158 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0126, Case 213.0126_pt.1, Case 213.0126_pt.2)
      Side A: Watch Yourself, Won't Let Her Go, Dying Words, Woman's Ways, Looking Through Me
    - Lloyd Quintet Fri June 29 '79 Max's 1st of ?/ Neon Boys '73, 1979/1973; ID: 213.0127; 198159 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0127, Case 213.0127)
      Side A: Misty Eyes
      Currently there is no access to this title. Please contact Fales Library.
    - Lloyd Quintet CBGB Thursday 13 Sept, '79 Part of Early Most of Late, 1979; ID: 213.0128; 198160 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0128, Case 213.0128_pt.1, Case 213.0128_pt.2)
      Side A: Blue & Grey, Woman's Ways, Misty Eyes, Just Like Smoke
    - Lloyd Dec 9, '79 CBGB Sunday Late, 1979; ID: 213.0129; 198161 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0129, Case 213.0129_pt.1, Case 213.0129_pt.2)
      Side A (Fall): Pretend
      Side B (Lloyd CBGB Dec 9th '79 Sunday Late): Tracks Unknown
    - Lloyd Dec 7, 8, 9th CBGB Friday Late, Sat Late, Sunday Early, 1975, ID: 213.0130; 198162 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0130, Case 213.0130_pt.1, Case 213.0130_pt.2)
      Side A (Lloyd CBGB Friday the 7th Late Show/Lloyd CBGB Saturday the 8th Late Show): [Track Unknown], I Can Tell, She's My Girl, Should Have Known, [Track Unknown], Alchemy, #9, Just Like Smoke, I Can Tell
      Side B (Sat Cont'd, Sunday Early): I Can Tell (cont'd), Summer Rain, Misty Eyes, She's My Girl, Watch Yourself, Get Off My Cloud, I Can Tell, Woman's Ways, Alchemy
    - Lloyd Oct 18th CBGB Thursday Late Show, 1979/ Dec 7, CBGB Friday Early '79, ID: 213.0131; 198163 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0131, Case 213.0131)
      Side A: Watch Yourself, In the Night, Blue & Gray, #9, I Won't Give her Up, Womans' Ways, Just Like Smoke, She's My Girl, Misty Eyes
      Side B: Dying Words, I Can Tell (Cut), Pretend, #9, Alchemy, Watch Yourselves
    - Richard Lloyd, Heat Dec 27, 28 1979 one set each night, ID: 213.0132; 198164 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0132, Case 213.0132)
      Side A (Lloyd- Heat Dec 2 1979/Lloyd Dec 28)
      Side B (Lloyd Cont'd)
    - Lloyd one set March 13 CBGB- snowstorm- Second Set March 15- 1980, ID: 213.0133; 198165 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0133, Case 213.0133_pt.1, Case 213.0133_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: She Said No, I Can Tell, Misty Eyes, Alchemy, Number/Nine, She's My Girl, Yes & No, Watch Yourself, [Track Unknown], She Said No
    - Patti Smith Dec 26 '75 Bottom Line, 1975; ID: 213.0134; 198166 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0134, Case 213.0134_pt.1, Case 213.0134_pt.2)
      Side A: Jessee James, We're Gonna Have a Real Good Time Together, Privilage, Ain't it Strange, Space Monkey, Redondo Beach, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Pumpin, Birdland, Land
      Side B: Gloria, Time Is On My Side, My Generation
    - [Based on Container Annotation]-- Patti Smith -Bottomline- Radio- Dec 27, 1975/[Based on Cassette Annotation]-- Side A: Roxy Music/ Side B June 1974, 1974/1975; ID: 213.0135; 198167 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0135, Case 213.0135_pt.1, Case 213.0135_pt.2)
      Content: [On container]
      Sides A and B: Real Good Time Together, [Track Unknown], Strained On Strange, Space Monkey, Redondo Beach, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Pumpin', Mafia, Land, Gloria, Time is on My Side, My Generation - Mummers Parade St Marks New Years Eve 1974-75
    - [Based on Container Annotation]--Patti Smith Columbia U April 1975/ [Based on Cassette Annotation]-- A) Kind Crimson's Lark's Tonight/B)Starless Bible Black, ID: 213.0136; 198168 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0136, Case 213.0136)
      Content: [On Container]
      Nigger, Seventh Heaven, Jeanne D'arc, What Make Ruda Ivory, Picasso Laughing, Sunday Evenings Down South, Rape, Rimbaud Dead, Born to be Me, Gilbrato, Christ died, All the Hipsters Have Gone to the Movies, Sonnett, Piss Factory
    - Patti Smith Live WBAI 1975, ID: 213.0137; 198169 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0137, Case 213.0137)
      Content: Lou 4/26/75 cont'd- Oh Jim- White Light/
      Sides A and B: Real Good Time, Hunter, Birdland, Redondo Beach, Space Monkey, Snowball, Distant Fingers, Break it up, Gloria, We Walk Down the Aisle of love
    - Television CBGB (Patti) '75 Rock's Tapes, 1975; ID: 213.0138; 198170 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0138, Case 213.0138_pt.1, Case 213.0138_pt.2)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Prove it, Venus, Friction, Blank, Double Exposure/Fire Engine, Prove it, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jane
      Side B: Friction, Kingdom Come/Real Good Time Together, Redondo Beach, Birdland, Space Monkey, Distant Fingers, Gloria
    - Patti Smith March 22, 1975 CBGB- Late show/ June 29, 1975 The Other End, March 22; June 29, 1975; ID: 213.0139; 198171 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0139, Case 213.0139_pt.1, Case 213.0139_pt.2)
      Side A: Hunter, Magellan, Piss Factory, We Three, Free Money, Break It Up, Land /Real Good Time, Redondo Beach, [Track Unknown]
      Side B: Birdland, Space Monkey, Snowball, Distant Fingers, Break It Up, Gloria, Time is on My Side, Piss Factory (encore)
    - Patti Smith Max's Sept 1, 1974- Patti-Vocal, Lenny Kaye-Guitar, R Shol- Piano/ Reno Sweeney Dec 9, 1973 Patti-Vocal & Piano, Lenny Kaye-Guitar, 1973/1974; ID: 213.0140; 198172 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0140, Case 213.0140_pt.1, Case 213.0140_pt.2)
      Side A (9/1/74): Real Good Time Marco, Polo, I'm Wild about That Thing, Harbour Spill, Hunter, Piss Factory, We Three, Land, Hey Joe, Speak Low, Autobiography, Seventh Heaven
      Side B (12/9/73): I Don't Love Nobody, Mon Vieux Lucien, Just An Accident, Sally, Jesse James, Annie Had A Baby, Ballad of the Bad Boy, 4 Interesting Positions, I Get a Kick Out of You, Piano Sacrifice, Steve McAvoy, Fire of Unknown Origins, Jimbo
    - Patti Smith- March 20, 1975 CBGB- Patti -vocal, Lenny Kaye- guitar, Richard Sohl-Piano, Ivan Kral -guitars, ID: 213.0141; 198173 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0141, Case 213.0141)
      Side A: Real Good Time, Redondo Beach, Sherry, Space Monkey, Birdland, Break It Up, Gloria
      Side B: Hunter, Just Like Magellan, We Three, Free Money, Distant Fingers, Land
    - Patti Smith Live at Reno Sweeney's, Max's, My Father's Place + single, 1973/1974; ID: 213.0142; 198174 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0142, Case 213.0142_pt.1, Case 213.0142_pt.2, Case 213.0142_pt.3)
      Side A (Reno Sweeney 29 Dec '73, Max's 1 Sept '74): We're Gonna Have a Real Good Time Together, Captured by the Game, Good Time, Gloria (version), Free Money, Break it Up, Horses, Piss Factory (single)
      Side B: Hey Joe (single), [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown],Jesse James, Annie Had A Baby, Ballad of a Baby Boy, I Get a Kick Out of You, Real Good Time
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request Part 1, Part 2, and Part 3.
    - Patti Smith -February 15th 1975 CBGB- Patti-vocals, Lenny Kaye-Vocal, guitar, Richard Sohl- Piano Bass, Ivan Kral- Guitar Bass, Tom Verlaine-Piano, February 15, 1975; ID: 213.0143; 198175 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0143, Case 213.0143)
      Side A: Real Good Time Together, Hunter, Birdland, Space Monkey, Break it Up, Gloria
      Side B: Any Day of the Week, Piss Factory, We Three, Free Moneym Harbor Spell, Land
    - Patti Smith Live at Cleveland's Agora, WMMS FM on Jan 26, 1976- Patti-vocals, Lenny-Guitar, DNV-Piano Ivan Kral-Bass Rhythm, Jay Dee Daugherty-Drums, John Cale - Bass (My Generation), January 26, 1976; ID: 213.0144; 198176 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0144, Case 213.0144)
      Side A: We're Gonna Have a Real Good Time Together, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Birdland, Break it Up
      Side B: Break it Up (cont'd), Land, Gloria, Time is on My Side
    - Patti Smith Live at the Hammersmith Odeon Featuring Tapper Zukie, Jah Don, October 23, 1976; ID: 213.0145; 198177 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0145, Case 213.0145)
      Sides A and B: Redondo Beach, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Ask The Angels, Time is on My Side, Pumpin', Aint it Strange, Gloria, Land of 1000 Dances
      Container Annotation: "Yea Pete that's me talking over radio Ethiopia might sound strange, but it got good reviews"
    - Patti Smith Live at the Roxy 1/30/76, January 30, 1976; ID: 213.0146; 198178 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0146, Case 213.0146_pt.1, Case 213.0146_pt.2)
      Side A: Tapper Zukie "Man ah Warrior", P. Smith "Hey Joe/ Pissfactory + assort.
      Side B (Patti Smith Live at Roxy 1/30/76) Realblood Time, Ain't it Strange, Redondo, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Birdland, Gloria, Kimberly
    - Patti Smith Group + friends, March 9th 1977, David Johansen, Tapper Zukie, Iggy, Paley Bros., Elliot Randall, Dougherty - guitars, A. Paley - Drums, Eric Rosenfeld (Manhattan Ocean Club), March 9, 1977; ID: 213.0147; 198179 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0147, Case 213.0147_pt.1, Case 213.0147_pt.2)
      Sides A: The Kids are Alright, You Really Got Me, No Jesterin', Parachute Woman X, The Pill X, Some Kinda Wonderful, Route 66*, Getting Married, Ain't it Strange ()
      Side B: Gimmie Some Lovin' [], 96 tears [], Use to Love Her, Can't Explain @ ^